<modules>
	<module name='mod_access'>Provides access control based on client hostname, IP address, or other characteristics of the client request.</module>
	<module name='mod_actions'>This module provides for executing CGI scripts based on media type or request method.</module>
	<module name='mod_alias'>Provides for mapping different parts of the host filesystem in the document tree and for URL redirection</module>
	<module name='mod_asis'>Sends files that contain their own HTTP headers</module>
	<module name='mod_auth'>User authentication using text files</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_anon'>Allows "anonymous" user access to authenticated areas</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_dbm'>Provides for user authentication using DBM files</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_digest'>User authentication using MD5 Digest Authentication.</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_ldap'>Allows an LDAP directory to be used to store the database for HTTP Basic authentication.</module>
	<module name='mod_autoindex'>Generates directory indexes, automatically, similar to the Unix ls command or the Win32 dir shell command</module>
	<module name='mod_cache'>Content cache keyed to URIs.</module>
	<module name='mod_cern_meta'>CERN httpd metafile semantics</module>
	<module name='mod_cgi'>Execution of CGI scripts</module>
	<module name='mod_cgid'>Execution of CGI scripts using an external CGI daemon</module>
	<module name='mod_charset_lite'>Specify character set translation or recoding</module>
	<module name='mod_dav'>Distributed Authoring and Versioning (WebDAV) functionality</module>
	<module name='mod_dav_fs'>filesystem provider for mod_dav</module>
	<module name='mod_deflate'>Compress content before it is delivered to the client</module>
	<module name='mod_dir'>Provides for "trailing slash" redirects and serving directory index files</module>
	<module name='mod_disk_cache'>Content cache storage manager keyed to URIs</module>
	<module name='mod_dumpio'>Dumps all I/O to error log as desired.</module>
	<module name='mod_echo'>A simple echo server to illustrate protocol modules</module>
	<module name='mod_env'>Modifies the environment which is passed to CGI scripts and SSI pages</module>
	<module name='mod_example'>Illustrates the Apache module API</module>
	<module name='mod_expires'>Generation of Expires and Cache-Control HTTP headers according to user-specified criteria</module>
	<module name='mod_ext_filter'>Pass the response body through an external program before delivery to the client</module>
	<module name='mod_file_cache'>Caches a static list of files in memory</module>
	<module name='mod_headers'>Customization of HTTP request and response headers</module>
	<module name='mod_imap'>Server-side imagemap processing</module>
	<module name='mod_include'>Server-parsed html documents (Server Side Includes)</module>
	<module name='mod_info'>Provides a comprehensive overview of the server configuration</module>
	<module name='mod_isapi'>ISAPI Extensions within Apache for Windows</module>
	<module name='mod_ldap'>LDAP connection pooling and result caching services for use by other LDAP modules</module>
	<module name='mod_log_config'>Logging of the requests made to the server</module>
	<module name='mod_log_forensic'>Forensic Logging of the requests made to the server</module>
	<module name='mod_logio'>Logging of input and output bytes per request</module>
	<module name='mod_mem_cache'>Content cache keyed to URIs</module>
	<module name='mod_mime'>Associates the requested filename's extensions with the file's behavior (handlers and filters) and content (mime-type, language, character set and encoding)</module>
	<module name='mod_mime_magic'>Determines the MIME type of a file by looking at a few bytes of its contents</module>
	<module name='mod_negotiation'>Provides for content negotiation</module>
	<module name='mod_nw_ssl'>Enable SSL encryption for NetWare</module>
	<module name='mod_proxy'>HTTP/1.1 proxy/gateway server</module>
	<module name='mod_proxy_connect'>mod_proxy extension for CONNECT request handling</module>
	<module name='mod_proxy_ftp'>FTP support module for mod_proxy</module>
	<module name='mod_proxy_http'>HTTP support module for mod_proxy</module>
	<module name='mod_rewrite'>Provides a rule-based rewriting engine to rewrite requested URLs on the fly</module>
	<module name='mod_setenvif'>Allows the setting of environment variables based on characteristics of the request</module>
	<module name='mod_so'>Loading of executable code and modules into the server at start-up or restart time</module>
	<module name='mod_speling'>Attempts to correct mistaken URLs that users might have entered by ignoring capitalization and by allowing up to one misspelling</module>
	<module name='mod_ssl'>Strong cryptography using the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) and Transport Layer Security (TLS) protocols</module>
	<module name='mod_status'>Provides information on server activity and performance</module>
	<module name='mod_suexec'>Allows CGI scripts to run as a specified user and Group</module>
	<module name='mod_unique_id'>Provides an environment variable with a unique identifier for each request</module>
	<module name='mod_userdir'>User-specific directories</module>
	<module name='mod_usertrack'>Clickstream logging of user activity on a site </module>
	<module name='mod_version'>Version dependent configuration</module>
	<module name='mod_vhost_alias'>Provides for dynamically configured mass virtual hosting </module>


	<module name='anti-contraband'>anti-spam module</module>
	<module name='Apache Proxy FastCGI'>proxy scheme module for FastCGI protocol...</module>
	<module name='Auth MemCookie'>Apache Cookie Authentification Module</module>
	<module name='Bandwidth Module'>Bandwidth and Connection control per Virtual Host or Directory</module>
	<module name='CPPSERV'>application server/servlet container with apache module that provide Java Servlet-like API and C++ Servlet Pages implementation to C++ programmers</module>
	<module name='DACS'>A light-weight, general-purpose authentication, authorization, and single sign-on system</module>
	<module name='gbap-pool'>stl allocator for apache memory pools</module>
	<module name='LDAP auth module'>HTTP basic authentication with LDAP</module>
	<module name='mod-apache-snmp'>SNMP module for Apache</module>
	<module name='mod-captcha'>mod-captcha is an Apache 2 module to prevent web sites from maliciosus software access. Developed in UNPSJB.</module>
	<module name='mod-ipenv'>set/unset environment variables based on client IP addresses or client hostnames.</module>
	<module name='mod-log-spread2'>rewrite from scratch to allow logging to use reliable messaging framework - spread</module>
	<module name='mod-wiki'>mod-wiki is a wiki as a module</module>
	<module name='modXLdapAuth'>X509 certificate authentication and LDAP authorization module</module>
	<module name='mod_accessibility'>filter for server or proxy to improve accessibility of web contents on-the-fly</module>
	<module name='mod_access_dnsbl     '>Access control based on DNSBL blacklists and whitelists.</module>
	<module name='mod_acronym'>Sample filter module for Acronyms</module>
	<module name='mod_activex_filter'>Enable ActiveX filtering for Apache proxy</module>
	<module name='mod_antispam'>by using this module, you can control referer spam accesses</module>
	<module name='mod_athena'>load balancer plugin for mod_proxy</module>
	<module name='mod_authnz_external'>Authentication provider using user provided scripts - secure authentication from Unix passwd file</module>
	<module name='mod_authnz_ibmdb2'>mod_authnz_ibmdb2 is an Apache authentication module using IBM DB2 as database for storing user and group information.</module>
	<module name='mod_authnz_sasl'>SASL socket based autnz module</module>
	<module name='mod_authn_dbi'>For Apache 2.1+ that uses libdbi to provide access to database backends, including MySQL, PgSQL, Oracle, and others</module>
	<module name='mod_authn_sasl'>Cyrus SASL authentication module</module>
	<module name='mod_authz_unixgroup'>Check access control based on membership in Unix groups</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_cookie_dbm'>Session authentication/expiration using (cryptographically strong) cookies. Cookie-to-username mapping with DBM database.</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_form'> Form-based, authorization module using MySQL and session management.</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_imap'>imap authentication module</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_msfix'>When MS XP Clients connect to WebDAV they may have a problem sending the user's name to Apache. This mod can fix the user's name</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_mysql'>MySQL-based authentication module with VirtualHost support (you need only one database for all VirtualHosts), now with SSL Support for the Connection to the MySQL-Server</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_openpgp'>OpenPGP Signature Verification for signed HTTP requests (see Enigform, mod_access).</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_oracle'>Authentication module for Apache 2.0 -> Oracle8/8i/9i</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_pam'>Add PAM authentication</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_pamacea'>Login form based auth module using PAM</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_pamport'>Provides PAM authentication. Module uses pamport to provide a flexible interface to PAM services.</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_phpbb'>auth by phpbb user and group</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_sim'>Authentication Session ID Management using MySQL and cookies.</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_timeout'>Idle timeout for basic auth/ldap auth.</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_token'>Token-based authentication similar to mod_secdownload in LIGHTTPD. Have your script generate a token and let Apache handle the file transfer without having to pipe it through a script for security.</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_useragent2'>Unsafe authentication for the Apache web server using the User-Agent</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_user_dir'>User directory based authentication</module>
	<module name='mod_auth_xradius'>RADIUS Authentication Module</module>
	<module name='mod_bt'>BitTorrent tracker implementation with PHP and Perl language hooks</module>
	<module name='mod_but V2.9 (Entry Server - SSO)'>MOD_BUT is a powerful entry server, including SSO, backend session hiding, shared memory session store, service authorization, authentication strengths and levels, login and logout features.</module>
	<module name='mod_bwshare'>Bandwidth throttling and monitoring per client IP address.</module>
	<module name='mod_caldav'>CalDAV RFC4791 module</module>
	<module name='mod_cband'>A virtual host bandwidth-limiting module provided to solve the problem of limiting virtualhosts and users bandwidth usage</module>
	<module name='mod_cbroker'>HTTP/CORBA gateway</module>
	<module name='mod_cfg_ldap'>Module that provides Vhost lookups via LDAP</module>
	<module name='mod_cguard'>simple and flexible connection limiter</module>
	<module name='mod_clamav'>Virus Scanning module for Apache2</module>
	<module name='mod_concat'>concatenate multiple files together in one URL request, similar to what perlbal does</module>
	<module name='mod_countm'>Counter returning count via jpeg or png image.</module>
	<module name='mod_cplusplus'>A C++ wrapper around apache-2.0</module>
	<module name='mod_crowd'>CROWD is a web-based single sign-on (SSO) tool for provisioning and identity management developed by Atlassian. This module allows for Basic authentication calls from apache over to CROWD SSO.</module>
	<module name='mod_csv'>Publishes CSV/spreadsheet data to the Web</module>
	<module name='mod_dav_acl'>RFC3744 (Access Control Rights)</module>
	<module name='mod_dav_svn'>Filesystem provider module distributed with Sub</module>
	<module name='mod_daytime'>RFC-867-compliant Daytime service</module>
	<module name='mod_dbd_mysql'>DBD Driver module for MySQL.   To replace mod_mysql_pool</module>
	<module name='mod_dbd_pgsql'>DBD Driver module for PostgreSQL.  To replace mod_pg_pool</module>
	<module name='mod_debug'>Gives an html-header with request-information</module>
	<module name='mod_diagnostics.c'>Debug tool for filters; aid to tracing buckets</module>
	<module name='mod_domaintree'>Mass virtual hosting module mapping host names to a directory tree</module>
	<module name='mod_dsp'>DSP - Davor Server Pages: PL/SQL Server Scripting + ORACLE AUTHNZ</module>
	<module name='mod_estraier'>mod_estraier is an apache module that registers web pages processed by the apache and search from them using the node API of Hyper Estraier.</module>
	<module name='mod_example_ipc     '>Sample code demonstrating shared memory and mutex usage in modules</module>
	<module name='mod_expat'>Filter module to turn XML into SAX buckets. This module has been replaced by mod_xml2 and will be no longer maintained.</module>
	<module name='mod_fcgid'>Apache2 module for FastCGI protocol</module>
	<module name='mod_footer'>add footer to certain pages with certain vars</module>
	<module name='mod_ftpd'>FTP Protocol module</module>
	<module name='mod_globule'>A module for server-to-server document replication. Clients are automatically redirected to one of the replicas.</module>
	<module name='mod_gridsite'>Grid authentication (GSI) and authorization (GACL, VOMS) in an Apache module</module>
	<module name='mod_highlight'>Syntax Highlighting in an Apache 2.0 Output Filter</module>
	<module name='mod_i18n'>Implements the i18n namespace to provide gettext translation as an output filter.</module>
	<module name='mod_idcheck'>Cookie based web authentication and single sign on system designed for largish</module>
	<module name='mod_ifier'>Apache2 request filtering and rejection</module>
	<module name='mod_injection'>Inject text after the HTML body tag.</module>
	<module name='mod_ip_count'>limit the number of requests to your server farm by incoming IP</module>
	<module name='mod_itp'>Implements  simputer  transfer protocol : ITP</module>
	<module name='mod_line_edit'>General-purpose fast text filter</module>
	<module name='mod_log50x'>Log error 500 - 509 to logfiles</module>
	<module name='mod_log_access'>customised, automatically rotated logs</module>
	<module name='mod_log_firstbyte'>New in performance testing! Enables you to log the time between the request being read and the first byte served.</module>
	<module name='mod_log_mysql'>Use one or more MySQL databases to log requests</module>
	<module name='mod_lua'>Module support LUA Script or html embbed LUA</module>
	<module name='mod_memcached_cache'>mod_cache provider module for memcached storage</module>
	<module name='mod_mldap'></module>
	<module name='mod_mono'>module ASP.NET for Apache</module>
	<module name='mod_mono'>Runs ASP.NET pages on Unix with Apache and Mono</module>
	<module name='mod_murka'>xml/xsl based web publishing environment</module>
	<module name='mod_oai'>Open Archives Initiative Protocol for Metadata Harvesting (OAI-PMH) support</module>
	<module name='mod_pgheader'>Replaces body tags with headers/footers</module>
	<module name='mod_prolog'>Embedded prolog interpreter</module>
	<module name='mod_proxy_html'>Fixup HTML Links for Reverse Proxy/Mirror</module>
	<module name='mod_proxy_xml'>Fixup Links in XML doc types (eg WML) for Reverse Proxy/Mirror</module>
	<module name='mod_publisher'>Universal markup processing filter</module>
	<module name='mod_python'>Apache/Python Integration</module>
	<module name='mod_qos'>Quality of service module implementing control mechanisms that can provide different priority to different requests.</module>
	<module name='mod_replace_regex'>replace text with regex pattern</module>
	<module name='mod_ruid'>based on mod_suid2 only for linux</module>
	<module name='mod_sasl_auth'>Module to allow authentication with sasl</module>
	<module name='mod_schema'>w3c/xml schema validator</module>
	<module name='mod_scheme'>Apache 2 module for Scheme language</module>
	<module name='mod_sesehe SEcure SErver HEader'>Modify or remove 'Server: ' HTTP response header. More on :  Module homepage</module>
	<module name='mod_setenvauthpw'>This module acquires a password from a request_rec structure body and incorporates it in an environment variable An environment.  An environment variable name is REMOTE_PASSWORD.</module>
	<module name='mod_spin'>Template engine, C API support via shared libraries, database connection pooling, persistent session/application data tracking</module>
	<module name='mod_sqil'>A RDBMS => XML mapper</module>
	<module name='mod_sql'>XML Namespace module to add SQL ops/queries</module>
	<module name='mod_ssi_func'>extensions to mod_include for math functions, random number generation, one step value pair variable setting and flastmod vars</module>
	<module name='mod_ssl_error'>X.509 certificate validation error trapping (SSL)</module>
	<module name='mod_suexec_helper'>Adds UserId and GroupId directives to apache which are passed as arguments to suexec when starting CGI scripts.</module>
	<module name='mod_suid2'>Suexec module for Apache2. it support chroot.</module>
	<module name='mod_swf2html'>Provides `glue between Apache 2 and Macromedia Flash Seach Engine SDK</module>
	<module name='mod_tee'>Clone a response as it is sent to the client</module>
	<module name='mod_tidy     '>mod_tidy is a TidyLib based DSO module for the Apache HTTP Server</module>
	<module name='mod_traf_thief'>This simple module allows you to redirect percent of traffic to your url.</module>
	<module name='mod_txt'>Display plain text files as prettified HTML with header+footer in the manner of directory indexes</module>
	<module name='mod_upload'>Input filter for file uploads (multipart/form-data)</module>
	<module name='mod_uploader'>High performance, low burdened apache-moduled uploader</module>
	<module name='mod_usertild'>UserTild Module</module>
	<module name='mod_valet_admin'>Site Valet Configuration and Admin Functions</module>
	<module name='mod_valet_audit'>Module for browser-based accessibility audit/reporting.</module>
	<module name='mod_valet_publish'>XML/XSLT publishing system for reports (POST, PUT, GET + XSLT)</module>
	<module name='mod_valet_report'>Site Valet Query and Browse Functions</module>
	<module name='mod_valet_sql'>Manage a dynamic pool of SQL connections</module>
	<module name='mod_valet_utils'>Utility module: Form handling and templatised report generation</module>
	<module name='mod_validator'>Markup Validation (HTML, XML, SGML) module</module>
	<module name='mod_vd'>A virtual domain to directory mapper. Fast variant of mod_vhost_alias.</module>
	<module name='mod_vhost ldap/pgsql/mysql module'>mod_vhost based on ldap/pgsql/mysql backend</module>
	<module name='mod_vhost_ldap'>Virtual Hosting from ldap built on top of mod_ldap (caching included). Module is now considered feature completed.</module>
	<module name='mod_vhost_mysql2'>Provides dynamically configured Virtual Hosting in Apache2.</module>
	<module name='mod_vhost_mysql2'>Provides dynamically configured Virtual Hosting in Apache2. With in Alias fabian@linuxno.de</module>
	<module name='mod_vhs'>Virtual Hosting Module that can get data from LDAP, MySQL, PAM, ... This module sets correctly the DOCUMENT_ROOT internal apache</module>
	<module name='mod_websh'>Tcl extension for rapid web application development</module>
	<module name='mod_wxjs'>Module for using JavaScript / wxWidgets as server-side language.</module>
	<module name='mod_xcap'>XCAP (RFC4825)</module>
	<module name='mod_xhtml'>Namespace module for XHTML (ensure W3C Appendix C) and SSI implementation</module>
	<module name='mod_xi'>partial XInclude implementation</module>
	<module name='mod_xml'>[obsolete] API/Framework for XML Applications with Apache 2.0</module>
	<module name='mod_xml2'>This module provides a filter to turn XML/HTML into a stream of sax buckets.</module>
	<module name='mod_xmlns'>Adds XML namespace support to publishing with Apache</module>
	<module name='mod_xsendfile   '>Serves alternative content by processing X-SENDFILE headers.</module>
	<module name='mod_xslt'>A Filter to parse xml with an xsl</module>
	<module name='mod_zrkadlo'>A database-backed mirror redirector</module>
	<module name='mon_mono'>Running .Net framework in cross-platform</module>
	<module name='vdbh_SQLite'>virtual host from SQLite3</module>
	<module name='Vhost Limit Module'>Allow to specify the max clients, per virtual host</module>
	<module name='xmlns_esi'>Parser for Edge Side Includes</module>
</modules>
